Faisal Fida

Islamabad, Pakistan



arainfaisal826@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/fasih4444



03408957390



https://fasih4444.netlify.app

Summary

Used MySQL, Django, and Python to create web apps additionally have understanding of HTML5, CSS3, PHP etc. Strong in Data Science and Machine Learning.

- Python API integration experience with Heroku's weather and time API.
- Be familiar with version control tools like GitHub

Experience



Freelance Software Engineer

Fiverr

Nov 2017 - Present (4 years 10 months +)

- > Data Science With Python
- > Python Neural Networks
- > Django Tutorial
- > SQL & AWS

Features Writer

Medium

Jan 2019 - Present (3 years 8 months +) Teaching & Producing Guides & How To's Gain Programming Knowledge & Skills

Education



Reader College Sargodha

Fsc, Pre-Engineering 2018 - 2020

COMSATS Institute of Information and Technology

Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Science 2020 - Present

Licenses & Certifications

- Python Programming for Beginners in Data Science Udemy
- Python Bootcamp 2020 Build 15 working Applications and Games Udemy